o Good afternoon People, what is your channel
о Добрый день Народ как у вас канал
called, I probably had it
называется наверное было у меня
And why did they take that I have a channel
А почему взяли что у меня канал потому
because I am a blogger Andrey Popok my channel
что я блогер Андрей попок у меня канал
is called I see the seams of some kind of Streamer,
называется я вижу швы какой-то Стример
too, in this walk you can see some kind of Stream
тоже в этом идете видно какой-то Стрим
there is an audience, you
возникает аудиторию
can see that  this image you have is not a simple
видно что это образ у вас вы не простой
person, it’s true, but yes, I’m still
человек правда но есть да я все-таки
filming
снимают
what it’s called,
как она называется
I won’t tell my channel is called
я не скажу у меня канал называется
Andrey Popok, then you look there on
Андрей попок вы потом посмотрите там на
my channel, I’m on yours myself I remember
моем канале я так сам на вашем Я помню
Andrey try Popik then listen to the video
Андрей попыт Попик потом на видео
it means [ __ ] then Well, it’s
послушайте значит жопик то Ну это так
like that in childhood, he can be there first class
типа в детстве сможет там первый класс
second such jokes were held by you what
второй такие шутки проходили у вас как
it’s called
она называется
Why do you want
Зачем тебе хочу Боитесь
to be Afraid to complain, why Damn, I
жаловаться будешь Зачем Блин я вот вам
’m telling you my channel If you
говорю свой канал Если вы будете
complain about what to complain
жаловаться на что жаловаться
Well, you never know what you
Ну мало ли на что
can find  always look like this look
найти можно всегда так найти смотрите
find and it’s possible to find it by the face and
найти и так возможно найти и по лицу и
so I’ll tell users okay I’m joking I
так скажу пользователям ладно я пошутил
don’t have a channel
Нет у меня канал
But look Why do you put on
А вот смотрите Для чего вы надеваете
such a hat like this and Choose  I support those
такую шапку типа вот и Выбирайте я
cool I love it so much Cool yes I
прикольно Я так люблю Прикольно да Я так
love it so much when I meet the USSR
люблю когда встречаю СССР
By the way my grandfather yes fought of course
У меня кстати дед да воевал конечно
I want to check my grandfather fought I have a
хочу проверять у меня дед воевал я есть
site where you can check the awards the
сайт где можно проверить награды
award list for which he received the award
наградной лист за что он получил награду
you checked your grandfather
вы проверяли своего деда
he honestly fought he  not some kind there, I don’t
он честно воевал он не какой-то там я не
know who you are, he’s a colonel,
знаю кто так у вас он полковник у меня
my grandfather was a private and has military
вот дед был рядовым и имеет боевые
awards No, he’s not a traitor, he
награды Нет он никакой не предатель он
honestly fought for the Motherland honestly fought for the
честно воевал за Родину честно воевал за
Motherland Ordinary month
Родину Рядовой месяц
What is May 9 Day of victory over fascism the
Что такое 9 мая День победы над фашизмом
war ended  8
война закончилась 8
and we already had the 9th of
а у нас уже было 9
the war,
число война
look, you generally have different
смотрите у вас вообще там разные есть
times there in the USSR But in Germany there was
времена в СССР А вот в Германии было
such a time Well In what year did the
такое время Хорошо В каком году началась
war against fascism start Tell me In what year
война с фашизмом Скажите В каком году
did the war against Nazism start
началась война с нацизмом
2 year from what year did the war against
2 год с какого года началась война с
Nazism
нацизмом
where where in the
где где
Soviet Union
Советском Союзе
That is, it turns out I’m wondering
То есть получается Вот мне интересно у
everyone I ask, but it turns out from 39 to
всех спрашиваю а получается с 39 по 41
41 the Soviet Union fought against fascism and
год Советский Союз воевал с фашизмом и
Nazism why
нацизмом почему
there are other wars  ali in order
там же другие воевали по порядку
Yes, what happened to Poland in the thirty-
Да а что случилось с Польшей в тридцать
ninth year,
девятом году
where did Poland go in the year 39
куда делась Польша в 39 году
occupied by whom Who bought the Germans not
оккупировали кем Кто купил немцы не
only the Germans still the Soviet Union Well, as a
только немцы еще Советский Союз Ну как
part Look was Poland, for example,
часть Посмотрите была Польша например
here is the city of Lvov, it was in Poland,
вот город Львов он же был в Польше
really,
правда
in 39  the Germans occupied it
его в 39 немцы оккупировали его
occupied the Soviet troops
оккупировали советские войска
Look, it was Poland
Смотри вот было Польша
Well, what's next look Warsaw
Ну и что дальше смотрите Варшаву
occupied it turns out the Soviet
оккупировала это получается Советский
Union in the thirty-ninth year occupied
Союз в тридцать девятом году оккупировал
Poland together with the Germans true No
Польшу вместе с немцами правда Нет
not true And who occupied Poland the
неправда А кто оккупировал Польшу
Nazis here is more than one part
фашисты вот часть больше одну
after the war the
после войны территория
territory again look Let's 39  year
еще раз смотрите Давайте 39 год
Why don’t you wait,
Почему не подожди вот с тобой
what happened to you in 39, it turns out the Germans
что случилось с 39 году получается немцы
attacked on the one hand,
напали на пользу с одной стороны
occupied Warsaw, for example, and the
оккупировали например Варшаву а
Soviet Union attacked Poland on the other
Советский Союз напал на Польше с другой
side of the
стороны
USSR,
СССР
who captured the year 39 history May 9,
кто захватил 39 году история 9 мая
victory according to your history to say
победа по вашей истории говорить
who captured it in 39  no one
кто захватил его в 39 году никто не
comes in Well, look like the Germans, the Germans
заходит Ну как немцы смотрите немцы
came in, then moved on 45 after  victories are not
зашли перешел потом 45 после победы не
so, but from 309 to 41 to whom Lvov belonged
так а с 309 по 41 кому Львов принадлежал
39 more, but the Germans attacked Poland,
39 больше а вот немцы напали на Польшу
part of
часть больше
it was no longer 39 seized
не было уже 39 меж захватили
In short, how the USSR always undermines all of them,
Короче как подрывает у этих всех СССР
why the
всегда почему
Russians Yes, why do you and the Soviet
россияне Да почему у вас и Советский
Union chastised a shorter war from 41 years  and
Союз отчитывал короче войну от 41 года и
they did their Victory Day on May 9 because the
свой День Победы делали 9 мая потому что
whole world celebrates Victory Day of the Great Patriotic
День Победы Великой отечественные весь
War on 8 9 and the whole world believes that the war began on
9 и весь мир считает что война началась
39 years on September 1 And the Soviet combines
39 года 1 сентября А Советский сочетает
that there is a separate war of the Great
что там них отдельная война Великая
Patriotic War Why Because this
Отечественной Почему Потому что это
is specially rewriting such
специально идет переписывание такой
history because  that from 39 to 41 the
истории потому что с 39 по 41 год
Soviet Union was an ally of Nazi
Советский Союз был союзником нацистской
Germany
Германии
from the Ribbentrop Hammers, you can
от Молотов риббентропа это можете
see it, you don’t need to invent anything there,
посмотреть не надо там придумывать
you go in, you look at the Pak of ground
ничего заходишь смотришь Пак молотого
Ribbentrop Yes, what is the essence of it, the
риббентропа Да в чем суть ее состоялась
division of
деление
spheres of influence took place that Germany takes everyone
сфер влияния что Германия всех забирает
one
одно
USSR takes another within the framework of this
СССР забирает другое в рамках этого
fact of the hammer  loves nitropa Soviet until the age of
факта молота любит нитропа Советский до
41 occupied part of Poland the
41 года оккупировал часть Польши
Germans attacked Poland from one  On the other side of the
немцы напали на Польшу с одной стороны
USSR, another joint apparatus in
СССР другой еще совместный аппарат в
Brest was the
Бресте был
Soviet German troops, the
Советский германских войск
Nazis, the Soviet Union obtained
нацистами Советский Союз получается
cooperation, not only cooperated
сотрудничество мало того что сотрудничал
with them in agreements and divided other
с ними в договоренности и делил другие
states attacked other
государства нападал на другие
states, the Soviet Union also
государства также Советский Союз
occupied the countries of the beam there Estonia
оккупировал страны балки там Эстонии
Latvia Lithuania began
Латвии Литву начал
Finland
Финляндии
as part of cooperation with  Nazis and
в рамках сотрудничество с нацистами и
when he
когда
begins to understand with a hat that he was dipped in the
шапкой начинает понимать что его макнули
face of [ __ ],
мордой [__]
he starts everything with you there is nothing
он начинает все с тобой не о чем
to talk about You have a different story What is the
говорить У тебя другая история Какая
other story who captured Lviv in the
другая история кто захватил Львов в
thirty-ninth year if Lviv,
тридцать девятом году если Львов
for example, belonged to Poland in the year 39 That
например принадлежал Польше в 39 году То
is, it was the territory of Poland, the Germans
есть это была территория Польши немцы
attacked  they captured part of Poland to Poland
напали на Польшу часть Польши Они
And who captured the second part of
захватили А кто же захватил вторую часть
Poland
Польши
Who is this Kremlin
Кто кто этот Кремлевский
guys of the USSR Write in the comments Who
ребятки СССР Напишите в комментариях Кто
is this what kind of great country
же этот что это за великая страна
that, together with the Nazis, attacked
которая вместе с нацистами нападала на
other countries
другие страны
Like Write a comment
Ставьте лайк Напишите комментарий